<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brazilian Jiu Jitsu on The Commonplace Book</title>
    <link>http://www.ralphrudd.com/docs/3-areas/brazilian-jiu-jitsu/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Brazilian Jiu Jitsu on The Commonplace Book</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.ralphrudd.com/docs/3-areas/brazilian-jiu-jitsu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>GFF 6 - Guard Passing</title>
      <link>http://www.ralphrudd.com/docs/3-areas/brazilian-jiu-jitsu/gff_6_guard_passing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.ralphrudd.com/docs/3-areas/brazilian-jiu-jitsu/gff_6_guard_passing/</guid>
      <description>John Danaher - Go Further Faster Volume 6 - Passing the Guard Fundamental Guard Passes:
 Double Under Pass Over Under Pass Knee Cut Pass Toreando Pass Leg Drag Long Step Pass Smash Pass  Nomenclature  Centerline: The line that bisects my opponent&#39;s left and right side. Left Diagonal: The line that runs from my opponent&#39;s right shoulder to his left hip. Right Diagonal: The line that runs from my opponent&#39;s left shoulder to his right hip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playing Guard</title>
      <link>http://www.ralphrudd.com/docs/3-areas/brazilian-jiu-jitsu/guard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.ralphrudd.com/docs/3-areas/brazilian-jiu-jitsu/guard/</guid>
      <description>Playing Guard No Gi Seated Guard Standing vs Seated Guard Options:
 Inside Position: Straight Hamstring (Headquarters) or Cross Hamstring (Cross Knee). Around the Guard (Double Outside Position): Toreando / X Pass. Over or Under the Guard: Rolling Kimura / Rolling Guillotine. Push back to Double Ankle or Double Under Grips.  Some Seated Guard Principles:
 Don&#39;t want to be on my back. So sit curled up, shoulders in front of the line of my hips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guard Passing</title>
      <link>http://www.ralphrudd.com/docs/3-areas/brazilian-jiu-jitsu/guard_passing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.ralphrudd.com/docs/3-areas/brazilian-jiu-jitsu/guard_passing/</guid>
      <description>Passing the Guard Guard Passing Positions These positions form the central nodes in my system of guard passing.
Full Staple:
 Left knee through, pointing in towards his hip. Toes hooked pointing out. His leg on my right shoulder, right hand Mid Straight Lapel Grip, right elbow tight. Head low, looking across far shoulder. Whole body oriented into him. Palm facing on left pants grip to defend against Ude Katame and Sankaku Jime.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>